{
    "subject": "Hiten_Tejwani",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Gauri_Pradhan_Tejwani",
    "human_readable": "Hiten Tejwani is married to Gauri Pradhan Tejwani.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858301281929016,
            "question": "Name a person married to Gauri Pradhan Tejwani."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.983299195766449,
            "question": "Who is married to Gauri Pradhan Tejwani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9803548455238342,
            "question": "Is Gauri Pradhan Tejwani married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9641768932342529,
            "question": "To whom is Hiten Tejwani married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9623320698738098,
            "question": "Is Hiten Tejwani married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9442898035049438,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Hiten Tejwani and Gauri Pradhan Tejwani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9355716705322266,
            "question": "Who are Hiten Tejwani and Gauri Pradhan Tejwani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8524388670921326,
            "question": "What is the name of Hiten Tejwani's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7217448949813843,
            "question": "Who are Hiten and Gauri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5652012228965759,
            "question": "What is the name of Hiten's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hiten Tejwani is married to Gauri Pradhan Tejwani.",
            "html": "yago_14085_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Hiten and Gauri?",
            "html": "yago_14085_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Hiten Tejwani's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_14085_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Hiten Tejwani and Gauri Pradhan Tejwani?",
            "html": "yago_14085_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14085_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can see that there are multiple mentions of Hiten Tejwani and his wife Gauri Pradhan in different documents. Here's the result:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references that Hiten Tejwani and Gauri Pradhan are indeed married. For example, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14085/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt` explicitly states \"Married to: Hiten Tejwani On: 4/29/2004\", and another document mentions they have been married for over 13 years. Therefore, the triple \"Hiten Tejwani is married to Gauri Pradhan Tejwani\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}